I've been going to WWDC since 2011.
The last time Steve Jobs spoke there,
and every year I try to guess,
is Apple going to come out with something completely new
or they only get about to make last year's thing
10% better.
When Apple first introduced ARKit, I was really excited.
But after a few versions, I started wondering,
what are they actually building toward?
Apple doesn't hire a bunch of computer PhDs
to develop some sort of technology
just for somebody to hold an iPhone up
until their shoulder gives out.
There had to be another piece of hardware in the works.
WWDC, when Apple finally announced the Vision Pro,
they showed it to us and we could look at it,
but we couldn't touch it, which was exquisite torture.
Once preo orders opened, I was on my iPhone immediately.
And on launch day, I picked up one
of the first Vision Pros in Dallas.